{
  "response": [
    {
      "question": "______  uses a hypervisor",
      "option1": "Virtualization",
      "option2": "Containerization",
      "option3": "Both",
      "option4": "Neither",
      "answer": "Virtualization"
    },
    {
      "question": "In ___________ environments, each application runs on its own kernel",
      "option1": "Container",
      "option2": "Virtual",
      "option3": "Both, container and virtual",
      "option4": "Neither container or virtual",
      "answer": "All of these"
    },
    {
      "question": " __________ uses images",
      "option1": "Virtualization",
      "option2": "Containerization",
      "option3": "Both",
      "option4": "Neither",
      "answer": "Both"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fewer physical servers are required, thanks to _________.",
      "option1": "Virtualization",
      "option2": "Containerization",
      "option3": "Both",
      "option4": "Neither",
      "answer": "Both"
    },
    {
      "question": "This splits up server resources to allow more than one operating system to run on one machine:",
      "option1":  "Public Cloud",
      "option2": "Hypervisor",
      "option3":"Computational fluid dynamics",
      "option4":  "none",
      "answer": "Hypervisor"
    },
    {
      "question": "Virtual machines virtualize",
      "option1":  "Hardware",
      "option2":  "Software",
      "option3":  "Kernels",
      "option4": "Operating systems",
      "answer": "Hardware"
    },
    {
      "question": "Containers virtualize",
      "option1":  "Hardware",
      "option2":  "Software",
      "option3":  "Kernels",
      "option4": "Operating systems",
      "answer": "Operating systems"
    },
    {
      "question": "An example of a hypervisor is",
      "option1":  "VMWare",
      "option2":  "Virtual Boxes",
      "option3":  "Kernels",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "Kernels"
    },
    {
      "question": " ___________ uses containers",
      "option1": "Container Nerd",
      "option2":"Docker",
      "option3": "Pod",
      "option4":"None of the above",
      "answer": "Pod"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ share the kernel of the host OS",
      "option1":  "Virtual machines",
      "option2":  "Containers",
      "option3":  "Disk images",
      "option4": "None of the Above",
      "answer":  "None of the Above"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a container?",
      "option1":  "4 milliseconds",
      "option2":  "5 minutes",
      "option3":  "25 hours",
      "option4": "6 days",
      "answer":  "25 hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is faster",
      "option1":  "Container",
      "option2": "Virtual Machine",
      "option3":"-",
      "option4":  "-",
      "answer": "Container"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is more Secure",
      "option1":  "Container",
      "option2": "Virtual Machine",
      "option3":"-",
      "option4":  "-",
      "answer": "Virtual Machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you run a VM in a container?",
     "option1":  "Yes",
      "option2":  "No",
      "option3":  "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer":  "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of below is not a dependency management tool?",
     "option1":  "Ant",
      "option2":  "Maven",
      "option3":  "Gradle",
      "option4": "Jenkins",
      "answer":  "Jenkins"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can we run Junits as a part of Jenkins job?",
     "option1":  "True",
      "option2":  "False",
      "option3":  "May be",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer":  "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which plugin allows jenkins to create pipelines?",
     "option1":  "JenkinsFile",
      "option2":  "Job DSL",
      "option3":  "All of these",
      "option4": "Pipeline",
      "answer":  "Pipeline"
    }
  ]
}